CHRIS SNYDER

(913)-485-7961 csnyder332@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/chris-snyderga csnyder332.github.io/CSnyder-Portfolio/

SUMMARY

Versatile professional with 8+ years of testing experience in Agile development environments. Seeking a Full Stack development role leveraging my experience with large-scale projects to create applications that are user-friendly and cost effective. Strengths in collaboration between teams, attention to detail, and pursuing new challenges.

TECHNI	CALS	SKILLS
--------	------	--------

•	Javascript	•	React	•	Node
•	HTML	•	SQL	•	Git
•	CSS	•	MongoDB	•	JIRA

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF KANSAS Certificate in Full Stack Web Development 06/2022

EXPERIENCE

BARTON SOLVENTS

Transport Driver, 07/2018 – Present

- Present bills and receipts and collected payment for products delivered
- Accurately maintain manifests for transportation of hazardous waste
- Maintain ELD daily for company and DOT compliance

EURONET WORLDWIDE

System Test Analyst, 11/2016 - 11/2017

- Writing SQL queries to pull data from databases and update tables
- Testing backend systems to verify accuracy of financial transactions and associated reporting
- Interacting with developers to explain software enhancements and re-test issues

EMPOWER RETIREMENT

System Test Analyst, 08/2012 – 11/2016

- Coordinating various types of User Acceptance Testing (UAT) including regression testing, system testing, integration testing, functional testing, data migration and validation
- Testing GUI features and verifying the functions of applications and IVRs through browser emulators
- Analyzing business requirements, functional specifications, developing test plans and strategies

ERICSSON/SPRINT

Business Analyst, 06/2000 - 04/2012

- Served as team lead of 8 associates that researched 911 address records for reporting
- Generated weekly reports of 911 address validation performance by Sprint and an outside vendor to upper management. This exercise provided the proof that Sprint is was the industry leader in 911 address validations
- Developed and maintained relationships with outside vendors providing enhancements to order processing systems